TripleLift Privacy Center
=========================

Last updated March 16, 2021

If you have a disability which prevents you from electronically accessing this policy and require it to be provided in alternative format (e.g., audio, large print), you can send us a message at our [contact](#contact) email listed below 

Our Privacy Center is designed to provide you with quick and convenient access to essential information about our privacy practices as well as to tools where you can express your preferences.

TripleLift is committed to transparency, and we want you to understand fully how we may collect, use and share information relating to individuals like you and how to access the privacy choices that are available to you. 

TripleLift Privacy Policies
---------------------------

To read our full privacy policies describing:

* How we collect, use and share personal information on this website and in our corporate activities, please see our [Website and Corporate Privacy Policy here](https://triplelift.com/corporate-privacy-policy/)
* How we collect, use and share personal information through our advertising technology, please see our [Advertising Technology Platform Privacy Policy here](https://triplelift.com/platform-privacy-policy/)

TripleLift Cookie Statements
----------------------------

To read about how TripleLift uses cookies and similar technologies to collect personal information about individuals:

* When you use or interact with our website or in our corporate business activities, see our [Cookie Notice here](https://triplelift.com/cookie-policy/)
* In the operation of our advertising technology platform, see our [Advertising Technology Platform Cookie Notice here](https://triplelift.com/advertising-technology-platform-cookie-notice/)

TripleLift Opt-Out
------------------

There are many ways to opt out of the collection and use of data for advertising which our clients may conduct using our technology. 

To express your preferences with respect to the information we may collect or receive about your device in our advertising technology, please visit our Opt-Out [here](https://triplelift.com/user-rights-policy-and-opt-out/).

To find out about alternative ways to opt out, see the section entitled [“Your Choices and Rights”](https://triplelift.com/platform-privacy-policy/#your-choices-and-rights) in our Advertising Technology Platform Privacy Policy.

Contact
-------

Please contact us at the email provided below if you have any additional questions or wish to make a complaint:

* About our collection, use and sharing of personal information on this website or in our corporate activities, please email privacy((at))triplelift((dot))com.
* About our collection, use and sharing of personal information through our advertising technology, please email platformprivacy((at))triplelift((dot))com.

### Company

### Resources

### Products

### Policies

### Certifications & Affiliations

Copyright © 2024 All Rights Reserved TripleLift  
53 W. 23rd St., 12th Floor New York, NY 10010

### Follow us!

### Stay Up-to-Date

Receive the latest news, trends and upcoming events.
